

INTERESTS

.Reading .Traveling

.Playing Games .Drawing

INTERESTS

.Autodesk Maya .Substance Painter .Meta Spark AR .Unity .Character Creator Unreal Engine

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Premiere

Adobe Illustrator

.Microsoft PowerPoint .Microsoft Word .Microsoft Exel

LANGUAGES

.Portuguese .English .Spanish

CONTACT

Lisbon (+351) 919 366 484 rita.simoes.saraiva@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/rita-saraiva-34a4b219a/

Rita Saraiva

AR VR Developer / 3D Artist

ABOUT ME

II'm a 22 year old, AR VR Dev/ 3D Artist/ UX UI Designer, with good communication, problem-solving, and great teamwork skills. I'm always eager to learn new things and find new ways to overcome my problems.

I have professional interests in the areas of 3D Modeling, Design, and AR/VR.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AR VR Developer

CYCLOID - FULLTIME NOVEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

·Creation of VR and AR Experiences.

.3D modeling - Creation of assets for applications and experiences in augmented reality and virtual reality

·Content Creation for Social Media

·Creation of experiences in augmented reality with Spark AR and 8th Wall .UX UI Designer

3D Artist / AR Developer

SPLINK - FULLTIME
OCTOBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2022

.Creation of 3D hyper-realist people

·3D modeling

·Video Editing

·AR Filters

·Content Creation for Social Media

·Creation of assets for applications and experiences in augmented reality

·Creation of experiences in augmented reality with Spark AR

Multimedia Designer / 3D Artist

LPM COMUNICAÇÕES - INTERSHIP + FULLTIME JUNE 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

Creation of audiovisual content such as:

- ·3D modeling virtual studios
- ·Podcast/event openers
- ·Video editing
- ·Character animation.

Freelance

FEBRUARY 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- · Creation of motion design content such as openers and informative videos.
- · Creation of 3D Models

Hostess

EUROCONGRESSOS - PART-TIME FEBRUARY 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2021

Attendance to the public, secretary work, development and design of delivery materials in congresses

EDUCATION

Video Games - Bachelor Degree

UNIVERSIDADE LUSÓFONA DE HUMANIDADES E TECNOLOGIAS SEPTEMBER 2018 - JULY 2021

Theoretical and practical training, technological and artistic in the areas of animation, digital games, video, multimedia communication, interactive arts and 3D modeling.